kirillwashere.com 2019-04-22

# PRIVACY POLICY – Kirill Was Here Store

**ORDERS**  If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (including name, telephone number, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and its expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

While making a purchase from assholesliveforever.com, you are given the option to create a username and password. This user name and password functionality offers our customers the ability to quickly and easily proceed through the check out process on repeat visits. We do not store your credit card information as part of this optional service. There is also the option to receive our email newsletter updates. If you choose to receive these you should expect weekly HTML newsletter content to arrive at the email address you provided with your purchase.

**USE OF INFORMATION**  We use the information we collect from you for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. We do not store your credit card information. If you have created a username and password to the site or if you have signed up to receive our email newsletter updates we may use your purchase history to personalize special offers and promotions for you. These offers and promotions will be delivered to you in the form of an email newsletter. 

**NEWSLETTERS**  If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe in our emails.

**LEGAL DISCLAIMER**  We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. You cannot opt out of disclosure of your personal information if required by lawful order.

**ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our My Account page, or by emailing our Customer Support at  **[help@lindafinegold.com](mailto:%20help@lindafinegold.com)**. 

**SECURITY**  The security of your personal information is important to us. We use reasonable technological and physical safeguards to protect personal information you provide to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, however, we make all reasonable efforts to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information. In the unlikely event of a data breach, you will be notified as soon as possible.

**USE/ACCESS BY THIRD PARTIES**  In addition to the third parties mentioned specifically in this policy, Linda Finegold / Kirill Was Here may share your information with third party vendors and affiliates. If LF / KWH shares your personal information with any third party, we will take precautions to ensure that these companies only use your information consistent with this Policy and that reasonable safeguards are taken to ensure the third party provides at least the same level of privacy protection that LF / KWH provides.

**COOKIES**  Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the website. 3rd party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes.
